[Music] let's
[Música]
see what's going on
a ver la movida k pasando
in the last few minutes
en los últimos minutos
Javier, click on Cely, it gets highlighted or you're
javier clic de cely que se tilde o que
freaking out and he deleted the live fast, damn,
flipas y borró el directo rápido ostia
look that up for me, Paulo in clips, can you put
búscame eso paulo en clips puedes poner
the option for the last 24 hours on the web?
la opción de últimas 24 horas a web
Good time, in May, okay, in the
buena vez a de mayo vale que en los
last few minutes
últimos minutos
several crazy people have grabbed bottles and
varios locos han cogido botellas y
went out to throw them because there were people who
salían a lanzarla porque había gente que
were saying that they had to drop them, it
estaba diciendo que había que soltar las
had reached me,
a mí me había llegado
okay, there's a melon demand, it had
vale hay demanda melón a mí me había
reached me that they had to throw the bottle
llegado que había que tirar la botella
because the guards were coming and how do you
porque venían los guardias y cómo te
register in the inventory they would kill you, I do
registrarse en el inventario te mataban
n't know if that was the reason, but there was
no sé si habrá sido ese el motivo pero
one who went back and
había uno
started throwing
que se han puesto a tirar de a tirar
bottles, okay,
botellas vale
and then there's a debate about whether that
y entonces pues hay un debate de si eso
's legal or not, whether you can throw
es legal o no de si se puede tirar
cans, whether you could kill when the lights were already
bote si se podía matar ya con la luz se
on or not, let's see what
encendía o no vamos a ver qué opina
Euros thinks about it,
euros al respecto
okay, here we have Pereira, okay, what
vale aquí tenemos a pereira ok que
theory is one of those who killed
teoría es uno de los que ha matado
when the lights were already on, let's
cuando ya estaban las luces encendidas a
see how it happened,
ver cómo ha sido
but I'll go with him, the 7th started to
pero irá conmigo el 7 se ha puesto a
pick up the bottles
recoger las botellas
the broken bottles there
las botellas rotas
was a moment in the live when
había un momento del directo en el que
I saw some of my team with a
yo he visto algunos de mi equipo con una
broken bottle and I said to him dude how do you
botella rota y le he dicho tío cómo
have it because you have a broken bottle and he
tiene porque tienes la botella rota y me
said I don't know I don't know we're not going when it
ha dicho no sé no sé no vamos a cuando
was wouldn't it be if Pereira fell what
ha sido no sería si a pereira caer que
happened to pick up the bottles that had already been
ha pasado de recoger las botellas que ya
thrown
se habían tirado
yes yes it's my team well Smith and those I
sí sí es mi equipo bueno smith y con los
'm with taking refuge upstairs [ __ ] we
que estoy yo refugiado arriba [__]
'll have to get away tomorrow if they go there
habrá que mañana alejarse si van allá
for him
por él
if the sun has gotten too hot or I have a thousand
si se ha calentado el sol o lo tengo mil
bottles the twizy clips that you see
botellas los clips de twizy que se ven
coming okay we were there
viene vale estábamos estaba todo el
everyone was throwing weapons at him well he
mundo tirando las armas a él pues las
was picking them up
estaba recogiendo
everyone is throwing weapons
está todo el mundo tirando las armas
because they were saying that the guards
porque estaban diciendo que los guardias
couldn't catch you that you had that in your
no te podían [__] que tuvieras eso en
inventory I don't know where that came from
el inventario no sé de dónde salió eso
okay I don't know where that came from but it
vale no sé de dónde ha salido eso pero
came out
ha salido
and despite it out
y a pesar la
there killing people
por ahí matando gente
the one below
el que tiene abajo
is consulting Laurel the legal loophole
está consultando laurel el vacío legal
not to
no
see in the series
haber en la serie
I think
creo
this is what happened in Greece
que esto es lo que ha pasado en grecia
to use let's see it's a game friends sometimes there
de usar a ver es un juego amigos a veces
are things that you don't really know if they are
hay cosas que no sabes muy bien si son
legal and  we have to make
legales y tenemos que ir tomando
decisions as we go along don't insult
decisiones sobre la marcha no insultéis
anyone or I'll be left with a brain drain let's
a nadie que me quede cojo la cabeza
not insult anyone please respect
no insultemos a nadie por favor respeto
everyone it's a game and as we
a todo el mundo es un juego y sobre la
go along like it happened in tortilla or in
marcha como ya pasó en tortilla o en
any other series things happen and we have to
cualquier serie pasan cosas y hay que ir
make decisions as we go along okay
tomando decisiones sobre la marcha vale
we've already made a decision about this
ya hemos tomado una decisión sobre esto
that you'll see tomorrow okay
que la veréis mañana vale
this one is okay nothing's happening things are happening we've
esta no pasa nada pasan cosas
already made a decision that you'll
ya hemos tomado una decisión que la
see tomorrow they're
veréis mañana
going to execute him I don't know if they should execute him I
lo van a ejecutar no sé si ejecutarlo
don't know if they should execute him but tomorrow the
no sé si ejecutarlo pero mañana irán los
guards will go and they'll catch him
guardias y los y lo cogerán
or they'll give him some more difficult test
o le pondrán alguna prueba más difícil
but it's that he's lost it like that we
pero es que se la ha ido a pérdidas así
were super good and I was another
estábamos súper bien y yo estábamos otro
refugee there
refugiado ahí
buffon even with greg I'll give you the
buffon incluso con greg te paso kit de
maximus kit reacting to your pop I'm going I'm
maximus reaccionando a tu pop
going friend
voy voy amigo
whoever can't copy it let's see it like that is that I can't I can't
el que no pueda copiarlo a verse así
copy it friends I ca
no pueda copiarlo amigos
n't copy it friends let's
no puedo copiarlo amigos
see why I catch it here directly no
a ver para pillo aquí directamente no
[Music]
[Música]
valid
valadez
people look
la gente mira
and what am I doing
y yo que hace
[Laughter]
[Risas]
[Music]
[Música]
checking something they're not checking
revisando algo no están revisando
the one who seems to be mediating it with a
el que parece que lo está mediando con
desert it's
desierto
difficult
difícil
the distraction  that
la distracción que se equipa
people are equipped, they look
la gente mira
totally with desire, this guy is
totalmente con deseos este tío está
saying this [ __ ] guy will lose outside,
diciendo este [__] perderá fuera
this one is saying and also you do
totalmente éste está diciendo y además
n't know, something is turned on and also it's with
no sabes algo encendido y además es con
the light, it's the day I owe it to him,
la luz es el día
with the light that day, ha ha ha ha ha what a pain in the ass to
lo debo fe con la luz ese día ja ja ja
be Catalan what a
ja ja vaya putada ser catalán
pain in the ass it's from the lights, I don't think there is
vaya putada es de las luces no creo que
pvp activated yet but just in case
haya pvp activado ya pero por si acaso
[Laughs]
[Risas]
and of course
y claro
and he supports the wedding, I'm going to see what
y él apoya en la boda voy a ver qué dice
these people say and
esta gente
I do people look at me
y yo de hace gente mira jo
and what do they do
y yo que hace
hahaha
jajaja
and decisions are made, that's it,
y se toman decisiones ya está no pasa
nothing happens but please we have to set an
nada pero por favor tenemos que dar
example, I think they're going to take it and they're going to
ejemplo yo creo que van a [__] y van a
go tomorrow, he's
ir a mañana va a aparecer él
going to appear, the soldiers are going to go for
van a aparecer los soldados van a ir por
Pereyra and I don't know if I don't think they'll
pereyra y no sé si no creo que lo
execute him, I think what they'll do will be
ejecuten yo creo que lo que harán será
one of the tests, bitching, be the most,
una de las pruebas putear se la más
something like that,
algo así
from the community that respects and hey, you can
de comunidad que respeta y oye tú puedes
give an opinion, hey, Pereira, I don't think
dar una opinión oye pereira no me parece
what you've done is right, okay, but please do
bien lo que has hecho ok pero por favor
n't insult because then you make
no insultos porque luego me dejáis mal a
me look bad, you know, then we get a bad reputation and we don't
mí sabe si luego pillamos mala fama y no
want that, we are spectacular people, damn, well, that's
queremos eso que somos gente
things that  They happen, okay, we talked about it with the
cosas que pasan vale lo hablamos con la
administration and I'll tell you, sometimes games
administración y ya te digo los juegos a
happen things that aren't
veces ocurren cosas que no están
planned, so of course you say now what do
planeadas entonces claro dices ahora qué
I do,
hago
what decision can we make? Well, that's what the
qué decisión podemos tomar pues para eso
administration is for, to watch the
está la administración para ver los
clips and make the right decision so
clips y tomar la decisión correcta para
that it's fair for everyone, okay,
que sea justa para todo el mundo vale
so tomorrow you'll see the decision that
así que mañana ya veréis la decisión que
the administration has made, which is not
ha tomado la administración que no soy
just me, there are many people and some who do
solo yo son muchas personas y algunos
n't even know about those deaths,
que ni siquiera conocer esas muertes ya
dog channels and real weight, role-playing
canales de perros y peso real tro de rol
silos,
silos
but what will it be to revive them, let's
pero que va a ser revivir los a ver a
see what I did, let's
ver que hice
see what Comanche says, but why do they
a ver qué dice comanche pero porque se
start fighting if that's a bridge to the
ponen a pelear si eso es puente a la
bottle forward, [ __ ] dog, I'm going to
botella hacia adelante [__] perro voy a
put, I
poner
mean, let's see what I ask for, I don't
o sea a ver que yo pide una cosa yo no
trust audio chat,
confío en audio chat
do the bed thing, there is,
hacer lo de las camas hay
I don't know how you go to bed on
es que yo no sé cómo se va a la cama a
the floors
los pisos
and they are chatting, they see it
y están chateando lo ven ellos
deciding on the click,
decidiendo sobre el clic
all the advise to the right,
todos los aconsejar a la derecha
whenever there is one there below, the
siempre que tiene ahí un abajo la
Cruzcampo factory invents the things
fábrica de cruzcampo inventa las cosas
that kill you, all the advise to
que te matan todos los aconsejar a
take off, they are telling him in their talk, they
despegar le están diciendo en su charla
even tell him there he goes and he tells him one day
incluso le dicen ahí va y le dice un día
and  will ask ibague by email
y pedirá a ibagué por email
says that
dice
the cha has to be deactivated very
es que el cha hay que desactivarlo muy
good if someone continues to be eliminated no I
buena si alguien sigue eliminado no yo
killed but inside the lights the lights
maté pero dentro de las luces las luces
off
apagadas
people
gente
what I
qué
have a thousand bottles
tengo mil botellas
this is unbearable that ong I
esto es infumable esa ong
see me
yo me ven
already I
ya
said it that we
es que lo dije
have a bottle again all
que tenemos botelho otra vez todos
and I
y yo
have a bottle again all of you who
tenemos botella otra vez todos
ingest it if I said it
los que os lo de ingerir si es que lo
ruben really well how do you throw the bottle at me
rubén re bien como me tiras la botella
dog
perro
but why do you start fighting
pero porque se ponen a pelear
thanks queen if that is can enter
gracias reina si eso es puede entrar a
the bottle forward [ __ ] dog for
la botella hacia adelante [__] perro por
I'm staying here I don't trust anyone
yo me quedo aquí yo no confío en nadie
chat you what happened don't look at me what I give you
chat tú qué pasó no me mires que te doy
this boy
este niño
like this explain a principle from the beginning
así explica un principio desde un inicio
we explain friends from the beginning we
explicamos amigos desde un inicio
explain we
explicamos
explain when there are guards
explicamos cuando haya guardias por
please do not disrespect them you
favor no les falten el respeto
have to give common sense that if you see
hay que dar el sentido común que si ves
guards entering it is not going to cause a mess
guardias entrando no va a hacer desmadre
ok you are
ok
not going to cause a mess you know
no vas a hacer desmadre sabes
when there are guards please respect
cuando haya guardias por favor respeto
not only the dick I don't know what to tell you day
no sólo la [__] no sé qué decirte día
in the squid game and you think they are
en el juego del calamar y crees que te
going to kill you
van a matar a ti
from  a child to someone the
de un niño a alguien
Andean truth
andina
I have a bottle
tengo una botella
[Music]
[Música]
already has two mini sar more serious suspenders
ya tiene dos mini sar más grave tirantes
to use I
de usar
have a thousand bottles and they are saying they
tengo mil botellas y están diciendo
are saying that they threw away the weapons or
están diciendo que tiraron las armas o
rather he also hears that he has the
sea el lo escucha también que tiene las
weapons there what he heard
armas ahí lo escuchado
and look throw throw away many bottles
y mira tira tira muchas botellas
if not that is wrong it is Pereira I am
si no eso está mal es pereira lo siento
very sorry friends imagine that is wrong that is
mucho amigos imaginaos eso está mal eso
wrong in the last
está mal en el último
that is very wrong they
eso está muy mal
told me that they will throw away the bottles
a mí me dijeron que tirarán las botellas
but I am quiet
pero yo me estoy quieto
whatever it will be
lo que sea será
clear
claro
now with the game over already when I was we are
ya con el juego acabado ya cuando estaba
going to the last seconds of finishing
vamos a los últimos segundos de terminar
the day
el día
rico and throw things
rico y tira las cosas
throw things and it is
tirar las cosas y ya está
clear throw the
claro tirar la
[ __ ] mother of
[__] madre
course if that is very bad that is very bad
claro si eso está muy mal
that was wrong
eso está muy mal eso sí estaba mal
sad it was
triste acababa
ending the day day 2 completed it
acababa el día día 2 completados
is out of the game already and everything and it is even
está fuera del juego ya y todo e incluso
out of the day the day is over
está fuera del día el día está terminado
and he did not kill rico and well Pereyra
y él no mató a rico y pues pereyra
Pppereyra was the one who killed him if that is
ppereyra fue quien lo mató si eso está
wrong
mal
but the guided exit completed he
pero la salida de guiado completado
has not died within the time
no ha muerto dentro del tiempo
that because it is a little bit of the game and if you
eso porque sea un poco el juego y si os
realize it is already finished you
dais cuenta está ya terminado me
understand the one who killed Buffet minutes
entendéis el que mató buffet minutos
before and has  sometimes entered the
antes y se ha entrado
fbi exhibits
exhibiciones del fbi
new dead friend
nuevo amigo muerto
live in london leave for cars
live in london dejáis para autos
to see what he says
a ver qué dice él
because the [ __ ] he kills him he needs but
porque [__] lo mata que necesita pero
you can see your voice
puedes verte la voz
here I picked up bottles and started to
aquí he cogido botellas y empezaba a
throw them and it's not
tirarlas y tampoco
harmful to see it's not anything
perniciosa verse tampoco tiene nada
serious either
grave tampoco
because I didn't want that
porque no quería
I find and digital marc and [ __ ] and
yo encuentro y digitales marc y [__] y
look the other way you know
mira para otro lado sabes
but here yes what I was going to do here I know what he's
pero aquí sí que iba a hacer yo aquí sé
going to do
que va a hacer
look how he takes the people to see
mira cómo se lleva a la gente
what he says now it gets complicated
a ver qué dice ahora se complica
installing the loop I know that in the end it
instalando la trabilla sé que al final
's from seeing a lot of people god let's
es de estar viendo muchísima gente dios
see what he says I don't know the virgin of the pillar
a ver qué dice no sé la virgen del pilar
what I don't understand why he tells me day 2
lo que no entiendo porque me pone día 2
completed
completados
because it's like that he's alone with the support of
porque es así él solo con el apoyo de
my brother
mi hermano
and bottom bunks you see
y literas de abajo se ve
today let's see let's
hoy
[ __ ] hell
[__] madre
yeah yeah well yeah imagine if you kill
sí sí bueno sí imaginar si matas a
graves this is the worst day and it was
graves que esto es lo peor día y fue sin
unintentional I'm sad
querer estoy triste
there I am it's today
ahí estoy es hoy
in fact it's that he throws 12
de hecho es que tira 12
and thrown and ricla and forgive me rich and
y tirados y ricla y perdóname rico y
forgive me I want to ask for your forgiveness he's rich
perdóname te quiero pedir perdón es rico
and new for you in fact he's not even going for anyone
y nueva por ti de hecho ni va por nadie
and you see the other  as it comes towards me and I have it in
y se ve la otra como viene hacia mí y me
common
la común
there is to take there we
hay para llevar ahí
will see again sometimes I put day 2
volveremos a ver a veces me ponía día 2
completed but
completado pero
this is what happened to the river and it charges me
esto es lo que le pasó al río y me carga
for work it also
por labor también
charges me for work too I
me carga labor también
think that
yo creo que
my bottle plus the bookstore appears your
mi botella más la librería aparece tu
drop
drop
what freaks me out is that I really have
lo que a mí me raya es que realmente yo
not pressed the left button
no he pulsado el botón izquierdo
and surely
y seguro que
yes we will
sí
see what it says you are
vamos a ver qué dice eres
because great truth to me that it is going to
porque gran verdad me que se la va
want to return they are
quiere devolver
not going to have to live I do not know what to
no van a tener que vivir no sé qué
tell you I think maybe to count
decirte yo creo que a lo mejor a contar
and like death
y como muerte
rich and throw things the
rico y tira las cosas
guards because they were shooting at
los guardias porque estaban disparando
who pays who here they were
a quién paga a quien aquí estaban
shooting the guards
disparando los guardias
of the virgin of the pillar Santom are
de la virgen del pilar santomé están
dancing I ca
bailando
n't be clear I
no puedo ser claro
went out to throw bottles like crazy man
salí a tirar botellas como loco tío
those shots that are were
esos disparos que son eran disparos
fake shots don't [ __ ] with time we were not
falsos no joda tiempo no te estábamos
thinking about you up there that they were that they were
pensando arriba que estaban que estaban
shooting at everyone who stopped
disparando a todo el que detenía
bottles in the inventory
botellas en el inventario
is that people were saying everything
es que la gente estaba diciendo de todo
- I like it count two or three that are
- me agrada cuenta dos o tres que están
the strip strip strip I can believe because the
la tira tira tira puedo creer porque el
pillar are dancing it ca
pilar están bailando
n't be it can't be it can't be
no puede ser no puede ser no puede ser
that their
que su crisis
nut crisis and is finishing of
de tuercas y está terminando de
include the fade to black
incluirse el fundido en negro
but it goes to the second day the completed
pero te va a segundo día los completado
god
dios
the server can't be can't be can't be can't be can't be can't be can't be
el servidor no puede ser no puede ser no
half completed number I can believe
amediados completado número puedo creer
because they killed him
porque lo han matado
but brother people we have completed it that's it
pero hermano gente lo hemos completado
everyone is already out of the
ya está ya está todo el mundo fuera del
server
server
who has died maybe not man what face does
quien ha muerto quizás no tío qué cara
he have like watson life
de tensión que tiene él como watson vida
all the lights
todo las luces
here he finds out what happened to pereira
aquí se entera de que ha sido de pereira
the second night and then I don't know I don't
la segunda noche y entonces no lo sé no
know I don't know very well what is going to
sé no sé muy bien lo que lo que va a
happen to me but now we'll see what
pasar yo pero ahora veremos a ver qué
happens I think that it will count
ocurre yo creo que sí que le va a contar
as a death according to what the man himself said
como muerte según lo que dijo el mismo
technically
técnicamente
technically it shouldn't count but
técnicamente no debería contar pero
according to the game it counted as a death
según el juego ha contado como muerte
because the counter has managed to count it
porque la ha llegado a contarle el
understand me although it has already been because of the
me entiendan aunque ha sido ya por el
game closing in the fade to black
juego cerrando en el fundido en negro
technically the game has
técnicamente el juego la ar la ha
registered it as a death
registrado como muerte
the game registers it as a death because
el juego lo registra como muerte porque
the counter came out
salió el contador
unless it is fixed tomorrow you have not
a no ser que mañana lo arregle no has
died he said as is the last
muerto ha dicho tal cual la última
death was unintentional it was not
muerte ha sido sin querer no era
intentional cappa is that I suppose 4
intencionada cappa es que yo supongo 4
I think that he did die today, it's
yo creo que sí que ha muerto hoy es
moderators because in the middle you can't
moderadoras porque en mitad no se puede
do this thing where people pass clips, I would
hacer esto de que la gente pase clips me
like people to be able to pass
gustaría que la gente pudiera pasar
clips, we can solve that, it's that I like that they
clips podemos solucionar eso es que a mí
pass clips suddenly look at
me mola que pasen clips de repente mira
you,
tú
my mother pp that had 50 bottles what a
madre mía pp que tenía 50 botellas que
damn terror she
maldito terror
's looking
está mirando
but what she's playing is from juan to the
pero que está jugando es de juan al
fort of rebel life of his look at
fortín de rebelde vida de su mira
bottles over here does this over here and
botellas por aquí hace esto por aquí y
this over there this over here
esto por allá esto por aquí
yes yes the way has gone a little and that is up
sí sí ha ido un poco la forma y que es
to here you're giving people the biggest
hasta aquí vas dando gente el mayor
terrorist
terrorista
the biggest terrorist you oh my god here
el mayor terrorista ti oh dios mío aquí
pp
pp lo mató
killed him let's see the death of carola nothing was playing he thinks he was still [Music] and here it says varela shot cloth shot and right click to kill is that no and transmit to the little sister in minecraft
y transmitir a la hermanita en minecraft
the one q see baritone
la q ver barítono
I feel very sorry for rico and because we have been
yo me da mucha pena por rico y porque
neither does he know the mechanics
hemos estado tampoco sabe las mecánicas
it's a [ __ ] really already to you it's that it
es una putada en verdad ya a ti es que
is very surprising no they don't explain anything to you
es muy sorprendente no no te explican
god don't touch don't touch any
hay que dios no toque no tocar ningún
button or touch anything dude I
botón ni tocar nada tío
mean and with a low profile
o sea y con un perfil bajo
that  what pereira has done he is going to look for
eso que ha hecho pereira va a buscar que
anyone tomorrow or the next night in
cualquiera mañana o la próxima noche en
the model to kill him look we
la maqueta lo maten mira nosotros
were there ricky gervais says let's
estábamos el ricky gervais dice vamos a
stick together with the days with these people
hacer piña con los días con esta gente
that we have next to us that was them the
que tenemos al lado que era ellos el
cref I do
cref
n't know them serious rico and this one that has
no los conozco grave rico y este que ha
died and I don't know who is serious and
muerto y no sé con quién está grave y
then I say to myself the grain the worth
entonces digo yo el grano la valía
the bastard evaporates troll
el cabrón se evapora trollear
to get in there and he's going to kill us I say to him
a meternos ahí y nos va a matar le digo
no no we are fine we are here I feel
no no estamos bien estamos aquí siento
all gathered quiet we are here well
todos reunidos quieto estamos aquí pues
this is over then he already sent us to spend
esto está pase después ya mandó a pasar
the night we were saying enriquillo well
la noche estábamos diciendo enriquillo
look you are going to spend the night and they haven't
pues mira ti va a pasar la noche y no
attacked us or anything you
nos han atacado ni nada
know so come on okay let's go
sabes entonces venga vale si vamos a
talk to them well we unite and
hablar con ellos bien nos unimos y
we are all okay but with what
estamos todos vale pero con lo que ha
pereira has done what is going to
hecho pereira ya lo que va lo que va a
happen is that anyone who crosses
pasar es que cualquiera que se cruce con
pereira he is going to kill him to get rid
pereira lo va a matar para quitárselo
of him you understand
del medio me entiende
but the mechanics too
pero las mecánicas también
carola himself says right click
el propio carola dice clic derecho clic
right click you know it's a shame but it was
derecho sabes es una lástima pero fue
so surprising what happens wait
tan sorprendente lo que pasa que espera
a little bit a business
un poco un negocio
look look I was perita
mira mira te estaba perita
and if I  you see oliveira this
y si yo lo veis oliveira
buffet this buffet
a esto lo de buffet esto lo de buffet
but pepe is a terrorist hey but
pero pepe es un terrorista oye pero
pereira 7 how many who has he made that he
pereira 7 cuantas quien se ha hecho que
is literally playing the way and
está jugando literalmente al forma y
way arena with a thousand points throwing
modo arena con mil puntos tirando
bottles that he is crazy look to
botellas que está mal de la cabeza mirar
[ __ ] off I
hacia a tomar por culo
saw him
lo he visto
but he doesn't stop throwing bottles he had
pero no para de tirar botellas que tenía
the inventory full of bottles the pp that thing
el inventario lleno de botellas el pp lo
about dying, [ __ ] that thing about dying from a blow is crazy
de morir [__] lo de morir de un golpe es
anyone could have died we have to
es que podría haber muerto cualquiera
wait here we have to wait a
hay que esperar aquí hay que esperar un
little
poco
what the [ __ ]
qué [__]
[Music]
[Música]
look at the moment in which pepe has been
mirad el momento en el que pepe ha sido
the biggest terrorist in history look
el mayor terrorista de la historia mira
at the moment in which pepe has been the
en el momento en el que pepe ha sido el
biggest terrorist in Venice yet and he was
mayor terrorista de venice todavía y
carrying
llevaba
look at his inventory look how is juan it
miren su inventario mirad cómo está juan
is that I find the tone funny like
es que me hace gracia el tono en plan
this for me
esto para mí
literally
literal
the whole bottles and 400 broken ones
las botellas enteras y 400 rotas
literally where people
literales donde gente
you already
usted ya
this work that I survived pinti 27
esta obra que sobreviví pinti 27
bottles fails what an outrage
botellas falla qué barbaridad
no well it doesn't say anything about you going for l
no pues no dice nada de que vayáis por l
download tweet clip
descargar clip de tweet
giles kids in the chat second day
chavales giles en el chat segundo día
completed few trusted but we are
completado pocos confiaban pero estamos
alive
vivos
when  the form is
cuando el formen
that real bro we have to do a
es que real hermano hay que realizar un
fun one
divertido
is that he respects [ __ ] and come and get together he is already
es que él respeta [__] y ven y junta ya
in the hospital man please come
está en el hospital tío por favor ven
son
hijo
find out about the chrome
averigüe el del chrome
a neighbor sees it no month in a row on
un vecino lo ve ningún mes seguido en
twitter and spoke to me
twitter y me hablo
now get well quickly
ahora se ponga bien rápido
an outrage what I just lived through
una barbaridad lo que acabo de vivir yo
here let's
aquí
see people I'm going to get into
a ver gente voy a meterme un momento a
evo la for a moment to see the amount of sulfur and
evo la para ver la cantidad de azufre y
explosives we have
de explosivos que tenemos
but because it was already out of time and
pero porque ya era fuera de tiempo y se
the lights had been turned on it could also
habían encendido las luces también puede
be now process that death rico already
ser ahora procesar esa muerte rico ya
dead I think they are going to leave him as
muerto yo creo que lo van a dejar como
dead but I don't know maybe he says
muerto pero no lo sé a lo mejor dice
well there he shouldn't have died
bueno ahí no debería de haber muerto
because it was already out of time and
porque ya era fuera de tiempo y se
the lights had been turned on it could also
habían encendido las luces también puede
be
ser
if I catch myself and fall out of bed he loses
si yo cojo y me caigo de la cama pierde
three hearts
tres corazones
okay he loses three hearts
vale pierde tres corazones
so
entonces
if I fell out of bed twice in a row
si yo me caído dos veces seguido de la
because I was half dumb
cama porque fui medio tonto
what happens death tells you because they died lie to you
qué pasa la muerte te cuenta porque han
so much you can die be it for
muerto mentirte tanto puedes morir sea a
me
mí
any decision I would wait tumor
cualquier decisión me la esperaría tumor
and if we are not still alive
y si no seguimos vivos
we advance to day 333 has died and I
avanzamos al día 333 ha muerto y yo
juana morzn peter carola there has been
juana morzán peter carola ha habido
big losses
grandes pérdidas
on the rope you're going to be more focused
en la cuerda vas a estar más concentrado
than me triads juan
que me tríadas juan
what test was the secret one I don't know it was
qué prueba era la secreta no lo sé era
the cookie and the night they haven't done
lo de la galleta y la noche no han hecho
any strange
ninguna rara
but when the bad thing about today is that we have
pero cuando lo malo de hoy es que hemos
waited too long there has
hemos esperado demasiado tiempo ha
been a lot of waiting to see if tomorrow
habido mucha espera a ver si mañana lo
we can do it faster the fewer
podemos hacer más rápido cuantos menos
players there are left the easier it will be
jugadores vayan quedando más fácil será
we started the day with about 121
hemos empezado el día con unos 121
how many will be left now guys
cuantos quedarán ahora chicos
Vince has died a few days not
ha muerto unos días vince no
to death a few days 15
a muerte unos días 15 no
are not 6 days
son 6 días
to death some videos that leave there are still
a muerte unos vídeos que irse todavía
left I always
quedan siempre
feel something and he has also died
siento algo y también ha muerto
like that the clip of Alex dying has passed
así ha pasado el clip de alex muriendo
I want to see it because you simply have to
quiero verlo porque simplemente tienes
record the people who die then
que grabar la gente que muere entonces
there you have some madness
ahí tienes una locura
well he hasn't said anything about going
bueno no ha dicho nada de que vaya a ir
after Pereyra and he hasn't said anything like
a por pereyra y tampoco ha dicho nada de
that either at least what have you
eso por lo menos qué es lo que me habéis
sent me I haven't said it I don't know what will happen
mandado no lo he dicho no sé qué pasará
but I'm telling you yoga pereira I'm
pero ya te digo yoga pereira
telling you that losing the battle for
ya te digo yo que perder la batalla por
him they are going to put
él van a poner a saco
a family to the test I'm looking forward to playing
una familia deseando estoy de jugar
tomorrow
mañana
and I know it's going to be the last day I
y sé que va a ser el último día
know it's going to be the last day tomorrow
sé que va a ser el último día mañana
but oh well  we will enjoy it pereira they
pero bueno lo disfrutaremos a pereira le
have more desire than your path you will say let's see let's see
tienen más ganas que tu camino dirás lo
tomorrow's tests
vamos a ver a ver las pruebas de mañana
tomorrow's tests are to see what
las pruebas de mañana son a ver lo que
you ask successes like toilet
preguntas éxitos como váter
but like how many things have they sent already
pero como cuántas cosas han mandado ya
no
no
how are you doing
cómo lo llevas éxitos
direct successes they have it more or less time
directos lo tienen más o menos vez
I imagine that Javier will be making an impressive video
me imagino que estará haciendo un vídeo
and declaring making the stars
javier y declarando haciendo los astros
and the 100 coffee to see it tomorrow's thing let's
y los 100 café a verlo lo de mañana a
see tomorrow
ver mañana
they say that it is the rope that where have they
dicen que es la cuerda que nos dónde han
said that
dicho eso
where have they said that that it is the rope
dónde han dicho eso que sea la cuerda
but that they don't know how to visit Greg's live they
pero que no saben visitar el directo de
are well
greg están bien
the rope realize that there are a
la cuerda date cuenta que hay muere un
lot of people dying
cojón de gente
because of that clip
por eso clip
or 10 and 10
osea 10 y 10
okay then I'll see who I ended up
vale entonces ya veré con quien terminó
joining with
uniéndome
in theory if I continue with light only said
en teoría si sigo con luz solo dijo
okay now we see the selling one now we
vale ahora vemos el de selling ahora lo
see it okay
vemos vale
if we did that link of
si hiciéramos lo de ese link
course tomorrow an elbow dies
claro mañana muere un codo
man
hombre
recited
recitó
okay you will be able to see what to add to those six
vale podrá ver que añadir a esos seis
minutes I will wait for you for a certain okay
minutos te espero de cierto vale
because we have to upload
porque hay que subirlo
the episode we already have the 3 to let's
el episodio ya tenemos el 3 haberle la
see what we give Naim Thomas
a ver qué damos naim thomas
this is me  symptoms
esta soy yo síntomas
require
requiere
pulse
el pulso
markey
markey
pp
pp
oak
roble
but there
pero no
are not 10 the rope I think there are 10
son 10 la cuerda creo que son 10
if we talk we
si hablamos
already talked about it the one with
ya lo hablamos
the rope that he had you can
el de la cuerda que ha tenido puedes
get out of the mess lino ol ol ol
salir del lío lino olé olé olé
ol ol
olé olé
from the rope that I don't know how it will be
de la cuerda que no sé cómo será
what we did here the other day with paula we
que hicimos aquí el otro día con paula
already saw to see
ya vimos a ver
if scioli oli
si scioli oli
the agreement and then the other one that they said they
el acuerdo y luego el otro que han dicho
said it was they
han dicho que era
told me it was
me han dicho que era
the other game
el otro juego
symptoms of 'operation triumph'
síntomas de la 'operación triunfo'
the crash chairs tomorrow seriously
las sillas de choque en mañana en serio
the being and they said now yes
el ser y han dicho ahora sí
maybe the hot potato
puede que la papa caliente
as if it were a hot potato that is
como si fuera una papa caliente eso es
running we
correr nos
could also survive it can
podríamos también sobrevivir puede
happen to us family that we do it well
pasarnos familia que lo hagamos bien
I, I have
yo
already fulfilled or Georgia with what with what I
yo ya cumplí o georgia con qué
lived I am happy
con lo que vivía me quedo contento
with what I lived I am happy
con lo que vivió me quedo contento
[Music]
[Música]